<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Pubky Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>https://pubky.synonym.to</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Pubky Knowledge Base</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>FAQ</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/FAQ</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/FAQ</guid>
    <description>Pubky Core - Frequently Asked Questions Table of Contents 1. Overview &amp; Philosophy 2. Architecture &amp; Resolution (PKARR, PKDNS, DHT) 3. Homeservers &amp; Hosting 4.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:19:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Readme</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Readme</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Readme</guid>
    <description>Pubky Knowledge Base Welcome to the Pubky Knowledge base - we are excited to have you here. 🔗 Access the Pubky Knowledge Base The current Knowledge base is a mix of reality, dreams, visions, actuality and plans.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:19:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>TLDR</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/TLDR</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/TLDR</guid>
    <description>Pubky App Pubky App is an open-source web application that helps users publish and consume Pubky homeserver data within a user experience that merges the features of popular social ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:19:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>The vision of Pubky</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/The-vision-of-Pubky</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/The-vision-of-Pubky</guid>
    <description>Decentralizing Our Future Imagine a future where our online relationships are no longer dictated by corporate giants or state-controlled systems, where you decide how to connect, ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:19:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Pubky Knowledge Base</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/</guid>
    <description>Welcome to the Pubky Knowledge Base This is a knowledge base for the Pubky platform, which includes Pubky Core, PKARR and Pubky App. These documents are a work in progress, much like Pubky’s protocols and applications! What is Pubky? Pubky attempts to unlock the web by realizing our vision for a key-based, self-regulating web that puts users in control.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:19:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>3.Protocols</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Explore/Pubky-Core/notes/3.Protocols</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Explore/Pubky-Core/notes/3.Protocols</guid>
    <description>Pubky Protocols This note is indicative and highly creative. We have not yet explored much about the open protocols that enable independent implementations: Pubky Data - Definition of normalized data schemas for user profiles, content types, relationships etc.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:19:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>DHT</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Explore/Technologies/DHT</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Explore/Technologies/DHT</guid>
    <description>Distributed Hash Table It is a decentralized key-value store that allows for efficient data retrieval in a distributed system. Unlike traditional databases, DHTs do not rely on a central server to manage data.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:19:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>DNS</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Explore/Technologies/DNS</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Explore/Technologies/DNS</guid>
    <description>Domain Name System It translates human-readable domain names (e.g., www.example.com) into IP addresses that computers use to identify each other on the network ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:19:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>DoH</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Explore/Technologies/DoH</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Explore/Technologies/DoH</guid>
    <description>DNS over HTTPS It is a security protocol that encrypts DNS queries and responses, enhancing privacy and security by preventing eavesdropping and tampering ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:19:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>HTTPS</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Explore/Technologies/HTTPS</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Explore/Technologies/HTTPS</guid>
    <description>Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure It is an extension of HTTP that encrypts communication over a computer network, enhancing security and privacy. It uses TLS (Transport Layer Security) or SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) for encryption, protecting against eavesdropping and tampering.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:19:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>