<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Pubky Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>https://pubky.synonym.to</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Pubky Knowledge Base</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>readme</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/readme</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/readme</guid>
    <description>:brain: Pubky Knowledge Base Welcome to the Pubky Knowledge base - we are excited to have you here. 🔗 Access the Pubky Knowledge Base: notes.pubky,app! The current Knowledge base is a mix of reality, dreams, visions, actuality and plans.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>vision</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/vision</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/vision</guid>
    <description>The Vision of Pubky: Decentralizing Our Future Imagine a future where our online relationships are no longer dictated by corporate giants or state-controlled systems, where you ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>index</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/</guid>
    <description>Welcome to the Pubky Knowledge Base This is a knowledge base for the Pubky platform, which includes Pubky Core, PKARR and Pubky App. These documents are a work in progress, much like Pubky’s protocols and applications! What is Pubky? Pubky attempts to unlock the web by realizing our vision for a key-based, self-regulating web that puts users in control.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>0.Introduction</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/0.Introduction</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/0.Introduction</guid>
    <description>Public-Key Addressable Resource Records Pkarr is a revolutionary system that bridges the gap between the Domain Name System (DNS) and peer-to-peer overlay networks ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>1.Why Pkarr?</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/1.Why-Pkarr</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/1.Why-Pkarr</guid>
    <description>This note explores the motivation behind Pkarr, addressing the challenges of distributed semantics, databases, and discovery. In pursuit of a sovereign, distributed, and open web, we identify three challenges: Distributed Semantics Everything expressed as keys and metadata Developing interoperable semantics for verifiable metadata about a set of public-keys that form a digital identity, complete with reputation, social graph, credentials, and more.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>2.Getting Started with Pkarr</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/2.Getting-Started-with-Pkarr</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/2.Getting-Started-with-Pkarr</guid>
    <description>This guide will help you understand how to publish and resolve resource records using pkarr. Publishing Resource Records To publish resource records for your key, you need to sign a small encoded DNS packet (⇐ 1000 bytes) and publish it on the DHT.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>3.Expectations</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/3.Expectations</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/3.Expectations</guid>
    <description>Understanding the expectations and limitations of pkarr is crucial for effective use. This note outlines what pkarr is not and what users should expect.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>4.Architecture</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/4.Architecture</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/4.Architecture</guid>
    <description>In-depth look at the architecture of pkarr, including its components and how they interact. Components Client: Applications or users that publish or query resource records.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>ELI5</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/ELI5</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/ELI5</guid>
    <description>ELI5: PKARR with Mainline DHT Imagine you have a super cool secret club, and everyone in the club needs a way to find each other and communicate without relying on anyone else to organize ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>1.Adoption</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/notes/1.Adoption</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/notes/1.Adoption</guid>
    <description>Pubky Adoption This note is indicative and creative. There is no set on stone plans for realizing adoption, these are just ideas. Realizing the full potential of Pubky relies on network effects through mainstream user onboarding: Legacy centralized imports ease migration paths for established communities and profiles.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>