<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Pubky Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>https://pubky.synonym.to</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Pubky Knowledge Base</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>readme</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/readme</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/readme</guid>
    <description>:brain: Pubky Knowledge Base Welcome to the Pubky Knowledge base - we are excited to have you here. 🔗 Access the Pubky Knowledge Base: notes.pubky,app! The current Knowledge base is a mix of reality, dreams, visions, actuality and plans.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>vision</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/vision</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/vision</guid>
    <description>The Vision of Pubky: Decentralizing Our Future Imagine a future where our online relationships are no longer dictated by corporate giants or state-controlled systems, where you ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>index</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/</guid>
    <description>Welcome to the Pubky Knowledge Base This is a knowledge base for the Pubky platform, which includes Pubky Core, PKARR and Pubky App. These documents are a work in progress, much like Pubky’s protocols and applications! What is Pubky? Pubky attempts to unlock the web by realizing our vision for a key-based, self-regulating web that puts users in control.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>4.Architecture</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/4.Architecture</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/4.Architecture</guid>
    <description>In-depth look at the architecture of pkarr, including its components and how they interact. Components Client: Applications or users that publish or query resource records.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>ELI5</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/ELI5</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/ELI5</guid>
    <description>ELI5: PKARR with Mainline DHT Imagine you have a super cool secret club, and everyone in the club needs a way to find each other and communicate without relying on anyone else to organize ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>1.Adoption</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/notes/1.Adoption</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/notes/1.Adoption</guid>
    <description>Pubky Adoption This note is indicative and creative. There is no set on stone plans for realizing adoption, these are just ideas. Realizing the full potential of Pubky relies on network effects through mainstream user onboarding: Legacy centralized imports ease migration paths for established communities and profiles.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>2.Incentives</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/notes/2.Incentives</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/notes/2.Incentives</guid>
    <description>Pubky Incentives This note is indicative and creative. Nothing is planned concretely for Pubky incentives. For the Pubky ecosystem to function at scale, it relies on incentives that encourage participation and uphold the user experience: Data storage fees pay stores for availability and throughput.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>3.Protocols</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/notes/3.Protocols</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/notes/3.Protocols</guid>
    <description>Pubky Protocols This note is indicative and highly creative. We have not yet explored much about the open protocols that enable independent implementations: Pubky Data - Definition of normalized data schemas for user profiles, content types, relationships etc.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>TLDR</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/TLDR</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/TLDR</guid>
    <description>Pubky App - TLDR Pubky App is an open-source web application that helps users publish and consume Pubky homeserver data within a user experience that merges the features of popular ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>DHT</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/DHT</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/DHT</guid>
    <description>Distributed Hash Table - DHT It is a decentralized key-value store that allows for efficient data retrieval in a distributed system. Unlike traditional databases, DHTs do not rely on a central server to manage data.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:45:36 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>