<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Pubky Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>https://pubky.synonym.to</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Pubky Knowledge Base</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>readme</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/readme</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/readme</guid>
    <description>:brain: Pubky Knowledge Base Welcome to the Pubky Knowledge base - we are excited to have you here. 🔗 Access the Pubky Knowledge Base: notes.pubky,app! The current Knowledge base is a mix of reality, dreams, visions, actuality and plans.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 07:49:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>index</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/</guid>
    <description>Welcome to the Pubky Knowledge Base This is a knowledge base for the Pubky platform, which includes Pubky Core, PKARR and Pubky App. These documents are a work in progress, much like Pubky’s protocols and applications! What is Pubky? Pubky attempts to unlock the web by realizing our vision for a key-based, self-regulating web that puts users in control.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 07:49:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>DHT</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/DHT</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/DHT</guid>
    <description>Distributed Hash Table - DHT It is a decentralized key-value store that allows for efficient data retrieval in a distributed system. Unlike traditional databases, DHTs do not rely on a central server to manage data.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 07:49:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>DNS</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/DNS</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/DNS</guid>
    <description>Domain Name System - DNS It translates human-readable domain names (e.g., www.example.com) into IP addresses that computers use to identify each other on the network ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 07:49:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>DoH</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/DoH</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/DoH</guid>
    <description>DNS over HTTPS - DoH It is a security protocol that encrypts DNS queries and responses, enhancing privacy and security by preventing eavesdropping and tampering ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 07:49:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>HTTPS</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/HTTPS</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/HTTPS</guid>
    <description>Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure - HTTPS It is an extension of HTTP that encrypts communication over a computer network, enhancing security and privacy ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 07:49:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Key Pair</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/Key-Pair</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/Key-Pair</guid>
    <description>A cryptography key pair consists of two related but distinct cryptographic keys: Private Key: A secret key that is used to decrypt, sign, or authenticate data ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 07:49:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Mainline DHT</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/Mainline-DHT</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/Mainline-DHT</guid>
    <description>Mainline DHT is a standard Distributed Hash Table (DHT) implementation widely used in the BitTorrent network, based on the Kademlia protocol. This decentralized system allows for efficient data storage and retrieval across a vast network of nodes, making it highly resilient and scalable.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 07:49:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Paykit</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/Paykit</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/Paykit</guid>
    <description>Paykit abstracts and automates any payment method behind a single, static public key. The public key belongs to a Pubky instance and points to a data store containing all supported payment endpoints.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 07:49:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Perspectives</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Perspectives</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Perspectives</guid>
    <description>Perspectives Users can save any custom-filtered view or feed as a “perspective” which is basically a custom template of settings of tags, weights, users, reach, and trends ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 07:49:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>