<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Pubky Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>https://pubky.synonym.to</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Pubky Knowledge Base</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>readme</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/readme</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/readme</guid>
    <description> The current Knowledge base is a mix of reality, dreams, visions, actuality and plans. When accessing the documentation on GitHub, please be aware that the content may not be fully represented.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:42:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>index</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/</guid>
    <description>Welcome to the Pubky Knowledge Base This is the Pubky Core and Pubky App knowledge base. Currently these docs are a mix of reality, dreams, visions, technicalities, actuality and plans.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:42:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>1.Web of Trust</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Concepts/1.Web-of-Trust</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Concepts/1.Web-of-Trust</guid>
    <description>The “Web of Trust” is a decentralized trust model used in cryptography, particularly in systems like PGP, GnuPG, and other OpenPGP compatible systems, to establish the authenticity ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:42:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>2.Censorship</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Concepts/2.Censorship</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Concepts/2.Censorship</guid>
    <description>Censorship in the digital age is a complex and multifaceted issue, affecting how information is shared, accessed, and controlled. It’s not just about blocking content; it’s about the power dynamics at play, the implications for freedom of expression, and the challenges of maintaining privacy and security in an increasingly interconnected world.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:42:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>3.Credible Exit</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Concepts/3.Credible-Exit</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Concepts/3.Credible-Exit</guid>
    <description>It is a concept that emphasizes the ability for users to leave a platform or service without being locked in, maintaining control over their data and experiences ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:42:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>ELI5</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/ELI5</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/ELI5</guid>
    <description>ELI5: Pubky Explained for Children Like a kite, data is in the cloud, but you hold its string. Your friends can find your messages by finding your kite in the sky (0.Introduction in the DHT) and following the string down to the message board you are currently posting on.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:42:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Aggregator</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/PubKy-App/Backend/Aggregator</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/PubKy-App/Backend/Aggregator</guid>
    <description>Pubky Aggregators Aggregators are specialized reducers or gatekeepers that continuously scan and collect data from various sources, such as data stores ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:42:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Indexer</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/PubKy-App/Backend/Indexer</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/PubKy-App/Backend/Indexer</guid>
    <description>The Indexer is a specialized component that plays a crucial role in the system by normalizing and transforming the aggregated data from multiple data stores into a unified view ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:42:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Introduction</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/PubKy-App/Backend/Introduction</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/PubKy-App/Backend/Introduction</guid>
    <description>The Backend is responsible for collecting (aggregators) and organizing (indexer) data from various sources, known as data stores. Imagine you’re trying to find a specific document in a large library.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:42:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Web Server</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/PubKy-App/Backend/Web-Server</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/PubKy-App/Backend/Web-Server</guid>
    <description>The system comprises a suite of backend services that orchestrate the integration of data feeds, search functionality, and user interface configurations ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:42:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>