<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Pubky Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>https://pubky.synonym.to</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Pubky Knowledge Base</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>readme</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/readme</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/readme</guid>
    <description>:brain: Pubky Knowledge Base Welcome to the Pubky Knowledge base - we are excited to have you here. 🔗 Access the Pubky Knowledge Base: notes.pubky,app! The current Knowledge base is a mix of reality, dreams, visions, actuality and plans.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:07:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>index</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/</guid>
    <description>Welcome to the Pubky Knowledge Base This is a knowledge base for the Pubky platform, which includes Pubky Core, PKARR and Pubky App. These documents are a work in progress, much like Pubky’s protocols and applications! What is Pubky? Pubky attempts to unlock the web by realizing our vision for a key-based, self-regulating web that puts users in control.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:07:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Paykit</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/Paykit</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Technologies/Paykit</guid>
    <description>Paykit abstracts and automates any payment method behind a single, static public key. The public key belongs to a Pubky instance and points to a data store containing all supported payment endpoints.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:07:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Layouts</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Layouts</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Layouts</guid>
    <description>Layouts Pubky client offers multiple customizable UI layouts for users that prefer different column, grid, and list layouts for their feeds.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:07:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Notifications</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Notifications</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Notifications</guid>
    <description>Notifications Pubky client tracks various event or activities the user may be interested in, and provides relevant notifications for interactions and other relevant activity ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:07:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Perspectives</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Perspectives</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Perspectives</guid>
    <description>Perspectives Users can save any custom-filtered view or feed as a “perspective” which is basically a custom template of settings of tags, weights, users, reach, and trends ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:07:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Posts</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Posts</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Posts</guid>
    <description>Posts In Pubkey client, a post is a message that a user publishes on the platform. Posts are the core content and they can contain a variety of information, including: Text: There is not text limitation of plain text, which can include words, phrases, sentences, or even just a single character.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:07:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Profiles</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Profiles</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Profiles</guid>
    <description>Profiles In Pubky client, a profile refers to a user’s personal page on the app, which displays their information, posts, and other content. A Pubky profile is a unique identity that represents a public-key.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:07:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Search</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Search</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Search</guid>
    <description>Search While Tags &amp; Filters are the primary sorting tools, the app also provides limited traditional search capabilities.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:07:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Tags</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Tags</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Client/Features/Tags</guid>
    <description>Tags They are keywords or phrases that are added to a tweet to help users find and engage with the content. Users can publicly assign contextual tags, like hashtags, to any other user or post.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:07:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>