<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Pubky Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>https://pubky.synonym.to</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Pubky Knowledge Base</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>readme</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/readme</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/readme</guid>
    <description>:brain: Pubky Knowledge Base Welcome to the Pubky Knowledge base - we are excited to have you here. 🔗 Access the Pubky Knowledge Base: notes.pubky,app! The current Knowledge base is a mix of reality, dreams, visions, actuality and plans.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:38:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>vision</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/vision</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/vision</guid>
    <description>The Vision of Pubky: Decentralizing Our Future Imagine a future where our online relationships are no longer dictated by corporate giants or state-controlled systems, where you ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:38:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>index</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/</guid>
    <description>Welcome to the Pubky Knowledge Base This is a knowledge base for the Pubky platform, which includes Pubky Core, PKARR and Pubky App. These documents are a work in progress, much like Pubky’s protocols and applications! What is Pubky? Pubky attempts to unlock the web by realizing our vision for a key-based, self-regulating web that puts users in control.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:38:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>ELI5</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/ELI5</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/ELI5</guid>
    <description>ELI5: Pubky App Imagine you’re at a massive party where everyone is sharing stories, showing pictures, and having interesting conversations. You get to decide who you talk to and what stories you listen to.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:38:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Introduction</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Introduction</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-App/Introduction</guid>
    <description> Synonym will be initially hosting: Data stores and Pubky App Overview Pubky-app’s initial focus is building a decentralized social media protocol. Key aspects Data Ownership: Users have full autonomy over their data, hosting it on independent data stores that are decentralized and distributed across the network.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:38:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>ELI5</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/ELI5</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/ELI5</guid>
    <description>Explaining Pubky Core Like You’re 5 Years Old Imagine you have a special toy castle that you built, and you want your friends to come and play with it ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:38:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Homeservers</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Homeservers</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Homeservers</guid>
    <description>The Pubky network allows multiple, independent data stores, known as “homeservers.” This improves censorship-resistance and prevents any single entity from controlling the ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:38:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Introduction</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Introduction</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Introduction</guid>
    <description>Pubky Core Overview Pubky Core is built on a few core concepts: Data Stores - Decentralized data storage nodes that host user data. Data is encrypted at rest.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:38:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>0.Introduction</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/0.Introduction</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/0.Introduction</guid>
    <description>Public-Key Addressable Resource Records Pkarr is a revolutionary system that bridges the gap between the Domain Name System (DNS) and peer-to-peer overlay networks ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:38:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>1.Why Pkarr?</title>
    <link>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/1.Why-Pkarr</link>
    <guid>https://pubky.synonym.to/Pubky-Core/Pkarr/1.Why-Pkarr</guid>
    <description>This note explores the motivation behind Pkarr, addressing the challenges of distributed semantics, databases, and discovery. In pursuit of a sovereign, distributed, and open web, we identify three challenges: Distributed Semantics Everything expressed as keys and metadata Developing interoperable semantics for verifiable metadata about a set of public-keys that form a digital identity, complete with reputation, social graph, credentials, and more.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:38:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>